<?xml version="1.0"?>
<resolution>
  <metadata xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <dublinCore>
      <dc:title>Step Up Women's Network for 15 years of contlbutlon to women</dc:title>
      <dc:publisher>Office of the Chicago Clerk</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>2013-03-13</dc:date>
      <dc:format>text/xml</dc:format>
      <dc:language>EN</dc:language>
    </dublinCore>
  </metadata>
  <main>
    <form>
      <date>6/6/2012</date>
      <sponsor>Mendoza, Susana A. (Clerk)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Graham, Deborah L. (29)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Smith, Michele (43)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Dowell, Pat (3)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Harris, Michelle A. (8)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Austin, Carrie M. (34)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Mitts, Emma (37)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Laurino, Margaret (39)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>O'Connor, Mary (41)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Lane, Lona (18)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Thompson, Joann (16)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Foulkes, Toni (15)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Silverstein, Debra L. (50)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Holmes, Natashia (7)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Hairston, Leslie A. (5)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Thomas, Latasha R. (17)</sponsor>
    </form>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Since 1981 every March the nation celebrates and recognizes the important contributions women have made to society; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, 15 years ago, Kaye Popofsky Kramer started Step Up Women's Network after finding out her mother was diagnosed with breast cancer; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, A Chicago office of Step Up Women's Network launched in '2006 and has since grown to 11,000 supporters mentoring 230 teen girls; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Step Up Women's Network ignites women and girls to fulfill their potential through after-school programs that empower teen girls, programming for professional women, and mentorship opportunities that connect both groups; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Step Up Women's Network focuses on building a confident, college-bound, and career-ready generation by working on increasing high school graduation and college acceptance rates for girls from under-resourced neighborhoods; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Teen girls involved in Step Up Women's Network programming receive 100 hours per year of enrichment programming and for three straight years 100 percent of Step Up seniors have graduated high school and been accepted to college; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Step Up Women's Network, with a national network of 50,000 women, has empowered and Inspired more than 1,000 teen girls in its 15 year history; now, therefore.</level>
    <level role="resolved"><heading>BE IT RESOLVED</heading>, That we, the Mayor and Members of the City Council of the City of Chicago, assembled this thirteenth day of March, 2013, do hereby honor Step Up Women's Network for its 15 years of helping all women and girls fulfill their potential and extend our wishes for many years of continued success; and</level>
    <level role="furtherResolved"><heading>BE IT FURTHER RESOLVED</heading>, That suitable copies of this resolution be presented to Step Up Women's Network.</level>
    <signature>Susana A. Mendoza, City Clerk</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Deborah Graham</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Michele Smith</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Pat Dowell</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Michelle A. Harris</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Carrie M. Austin</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Emma Mitts</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Margaret Laurino</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Mary O'Connor</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Lona Lane</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Joann Thompson</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Toni Foulkes</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Debra Silverstein</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Natashia Holmes</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Leslie A. Hairston</signature>
    <signature>Alderman Latasha R. Thomas</signature>
  </main>
</resolution>