<?xml version="1.0"?>
<resolution>
  <metadata xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <dublinCore>
      <dc:title>Tribute to late Daveda Renee Peeler</dc:title>
      <dc:publisher>Office of the Chicago Clerk</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>2012-12-12</dc:date>
      <dc:format>text/xml</dc:format>
      <dc:language>EN</dc:language>
    </dublinCore>
  </metadata>
  <main>
    <form>
      <date>12/12/2012</date>
      <sponsor>Mendoza, Susana A. (Clerk)</sponsor>
    </form>
    <statement>
      <preamble>
        <recital>A resolution</recital>
        <recital>adopted by The City Council</recital>
        <recital>of the Cityof Chicago, Illinois</recital>
        <enactingFormula>Presented by <fillIn><inline>Alderman Roderick T. Sawyer<inline> <inline>City Clerk Susana A. Mendoza</inline></fillIn> on <fillIn><date>December 12, 2012</date></fillIn></enactingFormula>
      </preamble>
    </statement>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>Whereas</heading>, the Members of this Chanriber were deeply saddened tp learn of the d^ath on October 24, 2012, at age 41, of baveda Renee Peeler, q respepted and valued staff member of the Chicago City Clerk's Office; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Daveda Peeler was born in Chicago on March 20, 1971 to Cecilia and David Peeler arid was their only chlid. Ms. Pei^ler attended^ Aeqderriic Center grammar sPhool, wds d imember of th^ Lindblpm Tiechnical High Sphool Class of 1989 and later attended the Indiana Institute of technology; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, On April 24, 1997, Daveda gave birth to a beautiful son, David, who was her pride arid joy and they shared a special mother-son bond. She was a vital member of her family and community, always ensuring family plans were completed well and on tjme; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Davedd served with pride ds q staff assistant in the Office of the City Clerk fpr more than 12 years. Ms. Peeler brought an enthusiasm to every position she held, inPluding as a Passport Acceptance Agent where she often repeived and cherished postcards from Chicagoans she assisted in receiving their passports; as an assistant in the Communications Division where she helped develop the first-ever Cjty Clerk Dog Day on the Green event; and most recently qs the assistant in the City Council division where she greeted everyone by name with her infeptidus smile; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Davedq qlso held positions with the Cook County State's Attorney's Office and H&R Block and recently completed her training tb be a certified mixologist; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Daveda was known throughout City Hqll for her willingness to cilwdys lend a hand, be qulpk.w|th a hug and q smile arid hier infectious Idugh arid enthusiasm. Ms. Peeler was a vivacious young woman who was a role model to her son and had d genuine love for life, her pommunity and the City of Chicago; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Dayeda is survived by her wondisrful son David, her beautiful mother Cecilia and her father David, her grandmother Hdttle Hill, and several dunts. Uncles, cousins and many friends; Daveda leaves behind her a legacy of fdjth, compassion, and love; now, therefore,</level>
    <level role="resolved"><heading>BE IT RESOLVED</heading>, That we, the Mayor and Members of the City Council of the City of Chicago, assembled this twelfih day of Depember, 2012, do hereby honor the life and memory of Daveda Renee Peeler and offer our condolences to hpr family and many friends; and</level>
    <level role="furtherResolved"><heading>BE IT FURTHER RESOLVED</heading>, That suitable copies of this resolution be presented to the family of Daveda Renee Peeler as d sign of our sympathy.</level>
    <signature>Rahm Emanuel</signature>
  </main>
</resolution>