<?xml version="1.0"?>
<resolution>
  <metadata xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <dublinCore>
      <dc:title>Declaration of April 30th, 2012 as "El Dia de los Ninos-Day ofthe Child" day in Chicago</dc:title>
      <dc:publisher>Office of the Chicago Clerk</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>2015-04-18</dc:date>
      <dc:format>text/xml</dc:format>
      <dc:language>EN</dc:language>
    </dublinCore>
  </metadata>
  <main>
    <form>
      <date>4/18/2015</date>
      <sponsor>Mendoza, Susana A. (Clerk)</sponsor>
      <sponsor>Solis, Daniel (25)</sponsor>
    </form>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, The greatest gift we will ever know is a child, born to love and grow. Making the world a better and safer place begins with young children. Children need emotional and physical stability and should not, ordinarily be separated from their parents; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Children need a safe and loving environment to grow, learn, excel and be happy. They are brilliant and ingenious in their own way. They try to depend on themselves to complete the task at hand. Their childhood is filled with bicycles and tricycles as well as bumps and bruises; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Dia de los Ninos (Children's Day) recognizes and acknowledges every child on earth. Children of the Latino community have much to contribute to the future of this city; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, Children bring happiness in the lives of their parents and relatives. They are th delicate and April 30 , Dia de los Ninos, commemorates the lives of our future pride and joy, our children. Children are a precious treasure, who will thrive on every hug and kiss. They will only be a child for a short time; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, More than 5,000 children and their families attend the Chicago Dia de los Ninos Parade each year. The parade strives to raise awareness about the importance of education for children; and</level>
    <level role="whereas"><heading>WHEREAS</heading>, This year the Chicago Dia de los Ninos Parade will be held on Saturday, April 28, 2012 kicking-off at Plaza de Tenochtitlan on 18th Street and Blue Island Ave and culminating at Harrison Park on 18th Street and Wood Street with a Fiesta; now, therefore,</level>
    <level role="resolved"><heading>Be It Resolved</heading>, That we, the Mayor and members of the City of Chicago City Council, th th day of April 2012 A.D., do hereby declare April 30 , to be El Dia de assembled this 18 los Ninos - Day of the Child in the City of Chicago.</level>
    <signature>Susana A. Mendoza, City Clerk</signature>
    <signature>Daniel Solis, Alderman, 25th Ward</signature>
  </main>
</resolution>